https://www.classic-modern.co.uk/privacy_policy

We use cookies to help the site function properly and to analyse traffic. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. For more information please review our Privacy Policy.
HomePrivacy PolicyNew in store
Vintage headscarf with concentric squares design in neutral colours, 1970s
£28.00
Vintage headscarf with links design in orange and brown, 1960s
£15.00
Vintage headscarf with geometric curve design in warm neutrals, 1960s
£20.00
Vintage headscarf with geometric design in reds and neutrals, 1970s
£25.00
Vintage headscarf with psychedelic design in pinks and browns, 1960s
£25.00
Vintage headscarf with psychedelic Vasarely-style op-art design, 1960s
£28.00Most-read blog posts
The real story of the Carl Thore lights
10/12/2012
0
Fog & Mørup’s iF Product Design Awards
20/05/2010
0
1960s prism lights by Werner Schou for Coronell
0
Looks like Bent Karlby for Lyfa, but isn't!
17/06/2010
0
Five of 100 great Danish designs of 1974
02/08/2010
0
The spiral that's not a Lyfa Weisdorf
22/07/2010
0Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.classic-modern.co.uk (“the Site”).Personal Information we collectWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.We collect Device Information using the following technologies:– “Cookies” data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages and date/time stamps.– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.How do we use your Personal Information?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfil any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
– Communicate with you;
– Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
– When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimise our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).Sharing your Personal InformationWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site – you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here. You can also opt out of Google Analytics here.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Your rightsIf you are a European resident you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfil contracts we might have with you (for example, if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.Data retentionWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.ChangesWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.Contact usFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at info@classic-modern.co.uk.
Loading...Loading...Loading...
